zzn.com 2018-12-28

# SERVICE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE

**NO UNLAWFUL OR PROHIBITED USE** |    
  
By using our services, you agree to the following Terms and Conditions: 

As a condition of your use of the Email Account/Services ("Services") and Sites ("Sites"), you will not use the Email Account/Services and Sites for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms, conditions, and notices. You may not use the Services and Sites in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair any Services or Sites (or the network(s) connected to any Services) or interfere with any other party's use and enjoyment of any Site/Service(s). You may not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any Services or Sites, other accounts, computer systems or networks connected to any Site/Service, through hacking, password mining or any other means. You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available through the Services.   
  
**USE OF SERVICES** |    
  
The Sites and Email Account/Services ("Services") contain e-mail services designed to enable you to communicate with others ("Communication Service"). You understand that all information, software, sound, graphics or other materials ("Content"), whether publicly posted or privately transmitted through the Services, are the sole responsibility of the person originating the Content. You are entirely responsible for all Content that you transmit via the Sites/Services. You agree to use these Sites/Services only to post, send and receive messages and material that are proper and, when applicable, related to the particular Communication Service. By way of example, and not as a limitation, you agree that when using a Communication Service, you will not: 

  * Use the Communication Service in connection with surveys, contests, pyramid schemes, chain letters, junk email, spamming or any duplicative or unsolicited messages (commercial or otherwise). 
  * Use the Communication Service to conduct any form of lottery or gambling, or to impersonate any person or entity. 
  * Defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or otherwise violate the legal rights (such as rights of privacy and publicity) of others. 
  * Publish, post, upload, distribute or disseminate any inappropriate, profane, pornographic, defamatory, infringing, obscene, indecent, abusive, threatening or unlawful topic, name, material or information. 
  * Upload files that contain software or other material protected by intellectual property laws (or by rights of privacy of publicity) unless you own or control the rights thereto or have received all necessary consents to do the same. 
  * Upload files that contain viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancelbots, , corrupted files, or any other similar software or programs that may damage the operation of another's computer or property of another. 
  * Advertise or offer to sell or buy any goods or services for any business purpose. 
  * Download any file posted by another user of a Communication Service that you know, or reasonably should know, cannot be legally distributed in such manner. 
  * Falsify or delete any author attributions, legal or other proper notices or proprietary designations or labels of the origin or source of software or other material contained in a file that is uploaded. 
  * Restrict or inhibit any other user from using and enjoying the Communication Services. 
  * Violate any code of conduct or other guidelines which may be applicable for any particular Communication Service. 
  * Harvest or otherwise collect information about others, including e-mail addresses. 
  * Violate any applicable laws or regulations. 
  * Create a false identity. 
  * Use, download or otherwise copy, or provide (whether or not for a fee) to a person or entity any directory of users or other user or usage information or any portion thereof. 

We generally do not monitor or edit the Content posted by users of the Communication Service. However, we may access your account and your mail to review materials posted to the Communication Service and to remove any Content that is posted in violation of these conditions of use or is otherwise inappropriate or objectionable. We reserve the right to terminate your access to any or all of the Communication Services at any time, without notice, for any reason whatsoever. 

We reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as we deem necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, in our sole discretion. 

Materials uploaded to a Communication Service may be subject to posted limitations on usage, reproduction and/or dissemination, you are responsible for adhering to such limitations.   
  
**STORAGE SPACE AND OTHER LIMITATIONS** |    
  
We may establish limits concerning the Sites ("Sites"), the storage of email messages, including the maximum number of days that email messages will be retained, the total number and/or total size (bandwidth used) of messages that may be sent from or received by an account, the maximum size of any email message and the disk space that will be allotted on our servers for an account. We may change these general limits without notice. We have no responsibility or liability for the deletion or failure to store email messages. Some messages may not be processed due to space constraints or outbound message limitations. You agree that we are not responsible or liable for the deletion or failure to store messages or other information.   
  
**TERMINATION/ACCESS RESTRICTION**

|    
  
No persons under the age of 13 may use the system and any persons creating accounts agree they are over 13. Due to the interactive nature of our site, and in order to comply with Federal laws designed to protect children on the Internet, we do not permit children to register on our site.

We may without notice modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, any or all of the Services. You agree that we will not be liable for any such modification or discontinuance of the service. 

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to terminate your account without notice to you at any time, with or without cause. Upon termination of your account, we may delete your email files and bar or restrict further access to Services. In the event of a paid account, we may terminate at any time and will only refund against certain criteria. 

We may also terminate or suspend your access to Services for inactivity, which is defined as failing to log into a particular service for an extended period of time, as determined by us. 

We shall have no obligation to maintain any content or to forward any unread or unsent messages to you or any third party.   
  
**NO SPAM** |    
  
We will immediately terminate any account which we believe, in our sole discretion, is transmitting or is otherwise connected with any spam or other unsolicited commercial (UCE) or other bulk email.   
  
**PRIVACY POLICY**

|    
  
Our policy is to disclose to you our information gathering and dissemination practices so that you may make informed decisions with respect to the disclosure of your personal information. 

**What Information We Collect**   
In using the Web Sites ("Sites"), you may be asked to provide us with various information. For example, when you register for an email account, or download software, you will be asked to provide your name, mailing address, phone number and e-mail address as well as certain other information. In addition, when you browse our Site or use our services, the choices you make may provide information concerning your interests or site visitors' areas of focus. 

**How We Use Information**  
We use the information you provide us to process requests, to provide notification about new or changed content or features, and for other purposes specific to activity at our Sites or use of the services provided. 

In addition, we may use e-mail addresses or other contact information for marketing purposes. For example, we may provide notification about new products or new services we or a partner are offering. 

**Cookies**   
Your Internet web browser has a feature called "cookies." Cookies allow us to recognize you while you are at our site. We use the minimum possible to provide our services and to maintain the security of your email account. If you disable the use of cookies, you will be unable to use the site. 

**Log Files  
**

We use and analyse our logfiles to gather aggregate information on usage of our services. Personal information is not used in this reporting. We may use the IP address of the system(s) you use to connect to the Services to improve our service and help diagnose any problems with our services.

**Links  
**This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Exceptions**   
There are two important exceptions to our privacy policy. First, we reserve the right to release or use personal information in connection with legal proceedings or in response to a subpoena or court order. Second, our policy only applies to information you provide to us. You may provide information to third parties if, for example, you click on third party advertising or a link to a third party site. We cannot be responsible for the conduct of these third parties. They may have policies concerning privacy and the use of cookies that differ substantially from ours. You may receive unsolicited messages from these third parties, or from others, due to this conduct. 

**Your Consent**   
By using the Sites and Services, you consent to our collection and use of information in accordance with this privacy policy. We may in the future decide to change this privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the change on this page so that you may always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and the circumstances under which we disclose it.
